<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on Fennel &amp; Dill</title><link>https://frosty-stonebraker-c9b5c7.netlify.com/categories/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on Fennel &amp; Dill</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Copyright Brook Shelley 2020</copyright><atom:link href="https://frosty-stonebraker-c9b5c7.netlify.com/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>on being alone</title><link>https://frosty-stonebraker-c9b5c7.netlify.com/posts/2014-3-4-on-being-alone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frosty-stonebraker-c9b5c7.netlify.com/posts/2014-3-4-on-being-alone/</guid><description>on being alone. A bit about this last few months.
It first hit me the night she left. The quiet. Before, there was rustling in the house, subtle signs of her presence, affection in the same space. Now, the night was too quiet, her form did not move with breath next to me. I was alone. My cats tried to fill the void. The wandered, and meowed, and looked for her in closets and cabinets — or so it seemed to me, as I projected my sadness onto them.</description></item><item><title>The Allure of the Minimal and Disconnected</title><link>https://frosty-stonebraker-c9b5c7.netlify.com/posts/2013-04-26-the-allure-of-the-minimal-and-disconnected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frosty-stonebraker-c9b5c7.netlify.com/posts/2013-04-26-the-allure-of-the-minimal-and-disconnected/</guid><description>The Allure of the Minimal and Disconnected The Future Most films that show our future are full of glitz and glamour, a fantastical land of flying vehicles. People live in clean, modern homes, and have their lives radically improved through technology, and want for nothing. Families and workers seamlessly keep in touch, and share parts of their lives with their friends and companions, and generally embrace the technology all around them.</description></item><item><title>xoxo 2015</title><link>https://frosty-stonebraker-c9b5c7.netlify.com/posts/2015-09-14-xoxo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frosty-stonebraker-c9b5c7.netlify.com/posts/2015-09-14-xoxo/</guid><description>XOXO 2015 XOXO Fest recap
This is my first XOXO, and as with many festivals or conferences where I know I might be overwhelmed, I was a little apprehensive. It helped so much that we had Slack setup for XOXO months in advance. I met tons of rad people in and around the tech industry while I was online, and then when the XOXO started, I was prepared with a group of new and old friends.</description></item></channel></rss>